{
  "sections": [
    {
      "title": "Log",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "Setup",
          "question": "**Setup**  \n",
          "answer": "1. [My Repo](https://github.com/atari-monk/roads-tutorial.git)\n",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-28T20:49:51.548Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Pomodoro 1",
          "question": "Pomodoro 1",
          "answer": "1. Graph visualized",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-28T21:32:31.413Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Pomodoro 2, 3",
          "question": "Pomodoro 2, 3",
          "answer": "1. Example of old ui, during building graph class.  \nEnds 48 min.\nFolder: old_ui_example",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-02T17:33:56.275Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Pomodoro 4, 5",
          "question": "Pomodoro 4, 5",
          "answer": "Starts 48 min.  \nFolder: editor  \nPomodoro 4: ended on distance in utils  \nPomodoro 5: ended on 1:10, on topic: dragging  points with mouse  \nOverall it was about how to write modern editor for mouse",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-03T20:08:55.218Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Pomodoro 6, 7",
          "question": "Pomodoro 6, 7",
          "answer": "Pomodoro 6:  \nstarts on 1:10, on topic - dragging points with mouse  \nPomodoro 7:  \nended on 1:28 (viewport, save)\n\n  ",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-03T22:51:30.970Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Pomodoro 8, 9",
          "question": "Pomodoro 8, 9",
          "answer": "start 1:28  \n2,5 pomodoro  \nended on 1:51 (finishing viewport)",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-04T12:13:31.373Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Pomodoro 10, 11",
          "question": "Pomodoro 10, 11",
          "answer": "Pomodoro 10:\nstart on 1:51 (finishing viewport)  \nPomodoro 11: ends on 2:07",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-05T13:07:54.893Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Pomodoro 12, 13",
          "question": "Pomodoro 12, 13",
          "answer": "Pomodoro 12: \nstarts 2:07  \nPomodoro 13:\nended on 2:28 (util methods)",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-06T15:52:24.469Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Pomodoro 14, 15",
          "question": "Pomodoro 14, 15",
          "answer": "Pomodoro 14:  \nstarts 2:28  \nPomodoro 15:  \nended on 2:47  \nthere is some bug, despite adding 1,5 pomodoro above 2 standard, i could not fixed it",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-08T10:34:50.394Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Pomodoro 16, 17",
          "question": "Pomodoro 16, 17",
          "answer": "fixed mistakes done in pomodoro 14,15, it was 3 typos, but hard to find,  \nnow i commit more offen, when it seems to work\nmade YT short video from this tutorial content",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-09T12:46:41.867Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Pomodoro 18, 19",
          "question": "Pomodoro 18, 19",
          "answer": "generating buildings along roads  \nended on 3:08",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-09T12:50:58.346Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Pomodoro 20, 21",
          "question": "Pomodoro 20, 21 ",
          "answer": "Pomodoro 20, 21 + fixes\n3:23",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-10T12:20:48.759Z"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}